Smoothie
yes sir
umm
Listen
No more Good boy, I'mma bad
Tak ada lagi Good boy, I'mma bad
Good boy これからはもうない I'mma bad
Good boy 이제 더는 없어 I’mma bad
Good boy ไม่มีอีกแล้ว I'mma bad
Good boy 从此不会再有 I'mma bad
Good boy 從此不會再有 I'mma bad
Good boy giờ không còn nữa I'mma bad
Softly Twist
Secara Soft, Twist
Softに Twist
Soft하게 Twist
Twist อย่าง Soft
Soft 地 Twist
Twist một cách Soft
Give you just a lil' taste ha
Give you just a lil’ taste ha
Whirl it up all without mercy then
putar tanpa henti lalu
容赦なく絞り切ってから
가차 없이 비틀어 논 다음
หลังจากปั่นอย่างไร้ความปราณีแล้ว
毫不留情地拧绞后
毫不留情地擰絞後
Sau khi bẻ quặt không ngần ngừ
Sip 'n' swallow
telan Sip
飲み込む Sip
삼켜 Sip
กลืนเข้าไป Sip
吞下 Sip
吞掉 Sip
Nuốt chửng Sip
Watch how I blend it up
We ain't picky, just happen to be thirsty
tak pilih-pilih, kami hanya sedang haus
何だって構わない 僕らはちょうど喉が渇いてた
가릴 것이 없어 우린 목이 말라 마침
ไม่มีอะไรต้องกังวล พวกเรากระหายน้ำ
我们不挑剔 刚好也口渴
我們不挑剔 剛好也口渴
Đúng lúc chúng ta đang khát nên không cần kén chọn
Show you this ruthless method you wanted
akan ku tunjukkan cara kejam yang kau inginkan
見せてやる 君が望んでた無慈悲なやり方
보여줄게 네가 바란 무자비한 방식
จะแสดงให้เห็น วิธีที่โหดร้ายที่เธอต้องการ
给你看你想要的无情方式
讓你見識 你渴望的殘忍方式
Hãy xem đây, phương pháp không từ bi mà em muốn
Strawberry sweet cinnamon
C'mon, go ahead Pop that corn
cepat Pop that corn coba ledakkan
早く Pop that corn 弾けさせてみろ
어서 Pop that corn 터트려봐
รีบระเบิดมันสิ Pop that corn
赶快 Pop that corn 爆开它
趕緊 Pop that corn 爆開它
Nhanh lên Pop that corn hãy làm nổ
You should know what you missin’
Your level is where you Guessin'
Guessin' sesuai tingkatannya
レベルに合わせて Guessin'
수준대로 Guessin’
ตามลำดับ Guessin'
按水平 Guessin'
隨著水準 Guessin'
Guessin' theo trình độ
Freeze like ice
One punch Crushin'
dalam sekali pukul crushin'
一気に Crushin'
단 한 번에 Crushin’
Crushin' ในทีเดียว
仅一下就 Crushin'
僅一次就 Crushin'
Crushin' chỉ với một lần
Raw, unedited Action
Action kasar
生のままの Action
날것 그대로인 Action
Action ที่ดิบ
毫无添加的 Action
毫無添加的 Action
Action như còn sống nguyên vẹn
Skin 'n' all, first we stompin'
pertama, injak kulitnya
まずは皮ごと踏み潰す
껍질째로 밟아 우선
เหยียบมันทั้งเปลือกก่อน
先连着皮一起踩
先連著皮一起踩
Trước tiên hãy dẫm lên cả da thịt
Countless cuts we'd suffer
luka yang ditahan terus-menerus
何度も耐え抜いてきた傷
수도 없이 견딘 상처
ทนกับบาดแผลอันนับไม่ถ้วน
向无数次忍耐的伤口上
向無數次忍耐的傷口上
Vết thương đã chịu đựng quá nhiều
Raise 'n' pour till it runneth over
Tuang ke atasnya sebanyak yang kau mau
その上に思いっきりぶっかける
위로 들이부어 실컷
เทมันลงไปให้จุใจ
尽情地倾倒
盡情地傾倒
Tha gồ đổ hết lên trên
Feels sticky on me
terasa lengket, membuatku
べったりと僕を
끈적하게 날
ความเหนียวที่ติดตัว
黏在我身上
Dính đầy mình anh
This Trauma tricklin' down me
menaiki Trauma yang mengalir
流れ落ちた Trauma
타고 흘러내린 Trauma
ไหลลงมา Trauma
顺着流下来的 Trauma
流淌而下的 Trauma
Chảy xuống từ trên người là Trauma
To the bottom, swallow it all chewy
kunyah dan telan sampai habis
噛みくだいて飲み込んで 底の果てまで
씹어 삼켜 바닥까지
เคี้ยวแล้วกลืนลงไป จนถึงพื้น
嚼碎吞下 直到底
Nuốt lấy cả mặt đất
Cuz you’re my
Smoothie
Smoothie Smoothie Smoothie
Shake it all in and blend it
Kocok dan haluskan semuanya
全てを入れて混ぜる
다 털어 갈아 넣어
เขย่ามัน แล้วบดให้ละเอียด
全部倒入后搅碎
全部倒入後攪碎
Nghiền hết cho vào
Smoothie Smoothie Smoothie
Dirty taste drink it up
Dirty taste Menenggak
Dirty taste 飲み干して
Dirty taste 들이켜
Dirty taste กลืนเข้าไป
Dirty taste 喝下
Dirty taste uống ừng ực
Smoothie Smoothie Smoothie
Chew a bit 'n' swallow it
kunyah perlahan dan telan
軽く噛みくだいて飲み込んで
가볍게 씹어 삼켜
เคี้ยวเบา ๆ แล้วกลืน
轻轻地嚼碎后吞下
輕輕地嚼碎後吞下
Nuốt chửng nhẹ nhàng sau khi nhai
Smoothie Smoothie Smoothie Smoothie
Sip it sip it down like Smoothie
Throw in that Doubt and fake
Masukkan semua Doubt and fake
ぶち込む Doubt and fake
때려 넣어 Doubt and fake
โยนเข้าไป Doubt and fake
全部倒入 Doubt and fake
全都加入 Doubt and fake
Cho hết vào đi Doubt and fake
Pour in all that Pain
Tuangkan seluruh Pain
注ぎ込んで　すべての Pain
쏟아부어 모든 Pain
ระบาย Pain ทั้งหมดออกไป
倾尽所有的 Pain
傾盡所有的 Pain
Đổ hết xuống tất cả Pain
Shower that in all this ice
Eventually it all melts, Fade out
Akhirnya akan mencair Fade out
結局は溶ける Fade out
결국엔 녹아 Fade out
ในที่สุดมันจะละลาย Fade out
终究会融化 Fade out
終究會融化 Fade out
Cuối cùng thì tan chảy Fade out
Go ahead toss in more Stuff
coba lempar lagi stuff
ほら もっと投げてみろ Stuff
어디 더 던져봐 Stuff
โยนเพิ่มอีกหน่อยสิ Stuff
尽管再扔试试 Stuff
盡管再扔試試 Stuff
Nào cứ ném tiếp xem Stuff
Syrup and sugar like buff
We make it easy
I’m gonna take it all
Ayo
Check it huh
More than enough ingredients
Bahannya melimpah
材料はありふれてる
재료는 차고 넘쳐
ส่วนผสมล้นเลย
材料多的是
材料多到滿溢
Vật liệu thì vẫn còn ngập tràn
Created this new Menu
Menu yang baru dibuat
新しく作った Menu
새로 만든 Menu
Menu ที่คิดขึ้นมาใหม่
新做的 Menu
全新打造的 Menu
Menu mới ra mắt
So delicious vicious
Say whatever, still I deserve
Apa pun I deserve
何と言っても I deserve
뭐래도 I deserve
ไม่ว่าใครจะพูดอะไรก็ I deserve
不管怎么说 I deserve
無論如何 I deserve
Dù sao thì I deserve
I’mma killa huh
What a commotion
Flecks fly up, splatter on clothes
ampas yang muncul, menempel pada pakaian
飛び散ったカスは服につく
튀어 오른 찌꺼긴 옷에 묻어
เศษซากที่กระเด็น ติดเสื้อผ้า
溅起的残渣沾在衣服上
噴濺的碎屑沾上衣服
Cặn bã bắn lên dính vào áo
Just get rid of it already
buang saja
捨ててしまう 僕はもう
그냥 버려 난 이미
ทิ้งมันไปเถอะ
我已直接扔掉
我已經索性扔掉
Thì anh bỏ đi không nuối tiếc
Don’t need permission
You just watch it
Shakin’ stirrin’ drinkin’ up
(ho! Give us some more)
Hot and spicy Mix it up
Wait stop
Close your mouth when you stare
Diam dan lihat
黙って見て
입은 다물고 봐
หุบปาก แล้วดูซะ
看的时候闭上嘴
看的時候閉上嘴
Cứ ngậm miệng lại trước đã
I’m ridin’ that new wave
You should know what you missin’
Your taste shows when Guessin'
Guessin' sesuai seleramu
好みに合わせて Guessin’
취향대로 Guessin’
ตามรสนิยม Guessin'
按喜好 Guessin'
隨著喜好 Guessin'
Guessin' theo sở thích
Freeze like ice
Mess up, rough it up (Rough that Mess up yeah)
Mess up dengan lebih kasar (lebih kasar Mess up yeah)
もっと激しく Mess up (激しく Mess up yeah)
더 거칠게 Mess up (거칠게 Mess up yeah)
Mess up ให้หยาบขึ้น (Mess up หยาบขึ้น yeah)
更粗暴地 Mess up (粗暴地 Mess up yeah)
更粗魯地 Mess up (粗魯地 Mess up yeah)
Mess up thô kệch hơn nữa (Thô kệch hơn nữa Mess up yeah)
Obvious, transparent Action
Action yang terungkap jelas
全部現れる Action
훤히 드러나는 Action
Action ที่ปรากฎให้เห็นอย่างชัดเจน
一目了然的 Action
清楚顯現的 Action
Lộ ra rõ ràng Action
View's all twisted distortion
pandangan menyimpang
ねじれた視線
배배 꼬여버린 시선
การมองที่บิดเบี้ยว
深深扭曲的视线
一再扭曲的視線
Cái nhìn rối bời éo le
Crush it, that's the Mission
menginjak adalah sebuah Mission
踏みにじるのが Mission
밟아버리는 게 Mission
Mission คือการก้าวต่อไป
彻底践踏就是 Mission
徹底踐踏就是 Mission
Giẫm đạp lên nó là Mission
We're a Special Edition
Kitalah Edition yang Special
僕らは Specialな Edition
우린 Special한 Edition
เราคือ Edition ที่ Special
我们是 Special Edition
我們是 Special Edition
Chúng ta là Special Edition
Felt sticky on me
terasa lengket, membuatku
べったりと僕を
끈적하게 날
ความเหนียวที่ติดตัว
看看黏糊糊地将我
看看黏糊糊地將我
Dính đầy trên anh
These scars once all over me
lihat bekas luka yang menutupiku
覆い尽くしてた傷跡を見ろ
뒤덮었던 흉터를 봐
รอยแผลที่อยู่บนตัว
覆盖住的伤痕
覆蓋住的傷痕
Hãy nhìn những vết sẹo đã được che phủ
End without a trace
Mengakhiri tanpa jejak
跡を残さないで終わらせる
흔적 없이 끝을 내지
จบแบบไร้ร่องรอย
毫无痕迹地结束
毫無痕迹地結束
Xử lý không còn một dấu vết
Watch me now
Smoothie
Smoothie Smoothie Smoothie
Shake it all in and blend it
Kocok dan haluskan semuanya
全てを入れて混ぜる
다 털어 갈아 넣어
เขย่ามัน แล้วบดให้ละเอียด
全部倒入后搅碎
全部倒入 攪碎 加入
Nghiền hết cho vào
Smoothie Smoothie Smoothie
Dirty taste drink it up
Dirty taste Menenggak
Dirty taste 飲み干して
Dirty taste 들이켜
Dirty taste กลืนเข้าไป
Dirty taste 喝下
Dirty taste 喝一大口
Dirty taste uống ừng ực
Smoothie Smoothie Smoothie
Chew a bit 'n' swallow it
kunyah perlahan dan telan
軽く噛みくだいて飲み込んで
가볍게 씹어 삼켜
เคี้ยวเบา ๆ แล้วกลืน
轻轻地嚼碎后吞下
輕輕地嚼碎後吞下
Nuốt chửng nhẹ nhàng sau khi nhai
Smoothie Smoothie Smoothie Smoothie
No matter the agony, I'm fine with it
tak apa untuk menderita sebanyak mungkin
どれだけ辛くても大丈夫
얼마든지 괴로워도 괜찮아
ทุกข์มากเท่าไร ก็ไม่เป็นไร
无论多么痛苦都无所谓
可以儘管痛苦也無所謂
Dù đau khổ mấy cũng không sao
Never did I expect only sweetness
ku tak pernah mengharapkan hal yang manis-manis saja
甘さだけを望んでたわけじゃない 僕は
달콤함만 기대한 적 없어 난
ไม่เคยคาดหวังแค่ความหวานอยู่แล้ว
我从来不曾只期待甜蜜
我從來不曾只期待美好
Anh chưa bao giờ mong đợi sự ngọt ngào
After all the pain melts and flows (After it flows)
setelah semua rasa sakit ini meleleh dan mengalir (setelah pergi mengalir)
すべての苦痛が何もかも溶けて流れた後 (流れた後)
모든 고통이 전부 녹아 흐른 뒤 (흘러간 뒤)
หลังจากความทุกข์ทั้งหมดละลายไหลไป (ไหลไป)
当所有痛苦全都融化后 (流走后)
當所有痛苦融化後 (流走後)
Sau khi mọi sự đau đớn đều tan chảy (sau khi trôi qua)
Fill me up again a whole new me
diriku yang baru terisi kembali
また満たされる新しい僕
다시 채워지는 새로운 나
กลายเป็นคนใหม่ที่เติมเต็มอีกครั้ง
重新被填满的全新的我
就會再次灌溉出全新的我
Lại đầy ắp lên một con người mới
Sip it down real smooth you know
Smoothie Smoothie Smoothie
Smoothie Smoothie Smoothie (Sip it down yeah)
Shake it all in and blend it
Kocok dan haluskan semuanya
全てを入れて混ぜる
다 털어 갈아 넣어
เขย่ามัน แล้วบดให้ละเอียด
全部倒入后搅碎
全部倒入後攪碎
Nghiền hết cho vào
Smoothie Smoothie Smoothie
Smoothie Smoothie Smoothie (Pour it like Smoothie yeah)
Dirty taste drink it up (Dirty taste drink it up Smoothie)
Dirty taste Menenggak (Dirty taste Menenggak Smoothie)
Dirty taste 飲み干して (Dirty taste 飲み干して Smoothie)
Dirty taste 들이켜 (Dirty taste 들이켜 Smoothie)
Dirty taste กลืนเข้าไป (Dirty taste กลืนเข้าไป Smoothie)
Dirty taste 喝下 (Dirty taste 喝下 Smoothie)
Dirty taste uống ừng ực (Dirty taste uống ừng ực Smoothie)
Smoothie Smoothie Smoothie
Chew a bit 'n' swallow it (Chew a bit 'n' swallow it Smoothie yeah)
Kunyah perlahan dan telan (Kunyah perlahan dan telan Smoothie yeah)
軽く噛みくだいて飲み込んで (軽く噛みくだいて飲み込んで Smoothie yeah)
가볍게 씹어 삼켜 (가볍게 씹어 삼켜 Smoothie yeah)
เคี้ยวเบา ๆ แล้วกลืน (เคี้ยวเบา ๆ แล้วกลืน Smoothie yeah)
轻轻地嚼碎后吞下 (轻轻地嚼碎后吞下 Smoothie yeah)
輕輕地嚼碎後吞下 (輕輕地嚼碎後吞下 Smoothie yeah)
Nuốt chửng nhẹ nhàng sau khi nhai (Nuốt chửng nhẹ nhàng sau khi nhai Smoothie yeah)
Smoothie Smoothie Smoothie Smoothie
Feels sticky on me
terasa lengket, membuatku
べったりと僕を
끈적하게 날
ติดหนึบกับฉัน
黏糊糊地将我
黏糊糊地將我
Dính lấy anh
Sip it sip it down like Smoothie
Sip it sip it down like
Smoothie